802 South County Road 23E Loveland, CO, 80537

I am a sophomore at the University of Colorado at Boulder, studying Engineering Physics and Applied Math. My goals are to go on to graduate school for physics and become a professor doing research in the field of atomic, molecular, and optical physics.

Education

Loveland High School GPA: 4.43 2011-2015

920 W 29th Street Honors Diploma, Summa Cum Laude

Loveland, CO, 80538 Salutatorian

University of Colorado GPA: 3.951 2015-Present

Boulder, CO, 80309 Engineering Physics, Applied Mathematics

Minor: Leadership Studies

Honors

CU Boulder Director's Club Scholar National AP Scholar (2015)

Boettcher Scholarship Semifinalist CU Engineering Honors Society (Tao Beta Pi)

CU Physics Honors Society (Sigma Pi Sigma) Discovery Learning Apprenticeship

Professional Experience

Resident Advisor 2016 – Present

I am a Resident Advisor in Andrews Hall at CU Boulder. Andrews Hall is home to the Engineering Honors Program; with which I am involved. This role involves being a support system and a mentor for residents living in the residence hall.

Assistant Laboratory Manager 2016 - Present

I am the assistant lab manager for the microfabrication laboratory at CU Boulder.

Lee Research Group 2015 - Present

I work as a research assistant on the thermal ground planes project with Dr. Y.C. Lee and Dr. Ryan Lewis in the Mechanical Engineering department at CU Boulder. My research is partly funded by the Discovery Learning Apprenticeship program of the Dean's office in the College of Engineering and Applied Sciences

Course Assistant 2017-Present

I host review sessions, write homework solutions, and grade for Matrix Methods in the Applied Mathematics Department at the University of Colorado.

Involvement

- Andrews Hall Book Club
- CU Presidents Leadership Class Sophomore Cohort Representative
- CU Engineering Honors Program Continuous Arm Chronograph Project Lead
- Tao Beta Pi Member (Engineering Honors Society)
- Sigma Pi Sigma Member (Physics Honors Society)